Karen Luu

Experienced Pharmacist

Drexel Hill, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Karen-Luu/3924dfe6d9f7231f

PA Licensed pharmacist offers 14 years of retail experience. Thorough knowledge of computerized drug-utilization evaluation, inventory management, and regulations governing pharmacy services. Serving as a liaison between health care professionals and the community to improve drug usage and therapeutic outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Walmart - January 2001 to October 2011

- Monitor and ensure adherence to proper procedures and guidelines for advising on, verifying, and dispensing pharmaceutical products.
- Counsel patients on health care and prescription medication needs.
- Communicate with physicians, nurses and other health care professionals on prescription clarification, drug information, drug incompatibilities, and appropriate equivalent products.

Pharmacy Manager

Kmart - Philadelphia, PA - 1999 to 2000

- Fill prescriptions and advise patients/customers in the proper use of prescription and non-prescription products.
- Monitor appropriate inventory levels and ensure all medications are properly stored and in-date.

Floating Pharmacist

Rite Aid, PA - 1997 to 1999

 Provide patients with accurate and efficient preparation of drugs according to the prescriber's request and assure accurate third party claims submissions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Temple School of Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA 1997